Guide to the George Starkovich Ephemera Collection
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- George Starkovich collection of sociopolitical pamphlets and papers, 1935-1957; 0305-001; 4.44 cubic feet 23 boxes
  - Pamphlets and Small Publications, Series 2
    - Speech at the 20th Congress of the C.P.S.U; A. I Mikoyan; Foreign Languages Publishing House - Moscow, 1956 (Box 8)
    - Speech at the 20th Congress of the C.P.S.U; V. M. Molotov; Foreign Languages Publishing House - Moscow, 1956 (Box 8)
    - Socialism: Utopian and Scientific; Frederick Engels; International Publishers, 1935 (Box 8)
    - Mastering Bolshevism; Joseph Stalin; International Publishers, April, 1937 (Box 8)
    - 30th Anniversary of the Great October Socialist Revolution; V. M. Molotov; Soviet News, Undated (Box 8)
    - The International Situation and Soviet Foreign Policy; V. M. Molotov; New Century Publishers, May, 1955 (Box 8)
    - Soviet Foreign Policy: The Meaning of the War in Finland; V. M. Molotov; New Century Publishers, April, 1940 (Box 8)
    - The Road to Power; Joseph Stalin; International Publishers, 1937 (Box 8)
    - Marxism Vs. Liberalism: An Interview; Joseph Stalin & H.G. Wells; International Publishers, 1935 (Box 8)
    - The Soviet Union and World Peace; Joseph Stalin & V. M. Molotov; New Century Publishers, July, 1946 (Box 8)
    - Stalin on the War and the Second Front in Europe; International Publishers, November, 1942 (Box 8)
    - Stalin's Policy of Peace and Democracy; V. M. Molotov; Soviet News London, 1948 (Box 8)
    - The Soviets and the Individual; Joseph Stalin; International Publishers, Undated (Box 8)
    - Mastering Bolshevism; Joseph Stalin; New Century Publishers, August, 1945 (Box 8)
    - On the Eve of October; V. I. Lenin; International Publishers, 1937 (Box 8)
    - Constitution of the U.S.S.R; The National Council of American-Soviet Friendship, Undated (Box 8)
    - Resolutions of the 20th Congress of the Communist Party of the Soviet Union; Foreign Languages Publishing House - Moscow, 1956 (Box 9)
    - Speech at the 20th Congress of the C.P.S.U.; D.T. Shepilov; Foreign Languages Publishing House - Moscow, 1956 (Box 9)
    - Speech At the 20th Congress of the C.P.S.U.; K.Y. Voroshilov; Foreign Languages Publishing House - Moscow, 1956 (Box 9)
    - Value, Price and Profit; Karl Marx; International Publishers, 1935 (Box 9)
    - Marxism Vs. Liberalism: An Interview; Joseph Stalin & H. G. Wells; New Century Publishers, September, 1945 (Box 9)
    - The Red Army; International Publishers, September, 1941 (Box 9)
    - Jews in the Soviet Union: Citizens and Builders; Paul Novich & J.M. Budish; New Century Publishers, May, 1948 (Box 9)
    - XXX Anniversary of the Great October Socialist Revolution; V. M. Molotov; Foreign Languages Publishing House - Moscow, 1947 (Box 9)
    - The Soviet Union and International Economic Cooperation; L. Fituni; Foreign Languages Publishing House - Moscow, 1952 (Box 9)
    - The Soviet People in the Struggle to Rehabilitate and Further Develop the National Economy of the U.S.S.R in the Postwar Period; Foreign Languages Publishing House - Moscow, 1952 (Box 9)
    - Decisions of the Central Committee, C.P.S.U.(B.) On Literature and Art (1946-1948); Foreign Languages Publishing House - Moscow, 1951 (Box 9)
    - The Part Played by Labor in the Transition from Ape to Man; Frederick Engels; International Publishers, 1950 (Box 9)
    - On the Question of Germany; V.M. Molotov & Marshal V.D. Sokolovsky; Information Bulletin, Embassy of the Union of Soviet Socialist Republics, December, 1947 (Box 9)
    - On Changes In the Rules of the Communist Party of the Soviet Union; N. Khrushchev; New Century Publishers, January, 1953 (Box 9)
    - A Soviet Automatic Plant; A. Erivansky; Foreign Languages Publishing House - Moscow, 1955 (Box 9)
    - My Answer, to an American Questionnaire; Praskovya Angelina; Foreign Languages Publishing House - Moscow, 1949 (Box 9)
    - Briefly About the Disagreements in The Party; Joseph Stalin & H. G. Wells; Foreign Languages Publishing House - Moscow, 1952 (Box 9)
    - From the February Revolution to the October Revolution 1917; A. F. Ilyin-Genevsky; International Publishers, 1931 (Box 9)
    - From Socialism to Communism in the Soviet Union; Joseph Stalin; International Publishers, Undated (Box 9)
    - the Teachings of Karl Marx; V. I. Lenin; International Publishers, 1930 (Box 9)
    - Social Insurance in the USSR; Z. Mokhov; Soviet News, 1945 (Box 9)
    - Trotskyism: in the Service of Fascism Against Socialism and Peace; A.Y. Vyshinsky; International Publishers, 1936 (Box 9)
    - The Science of Hatred; Mikhail Sholokhov; New Age Publishers: New York, January, 1943 (Box 9)
    - Our Debt to Our Soviet Ally; Joseph E. Davies; Soviet Russia Today, Undated (Box 9)
    - Soviet Democracy; Harry F. Ward; Soviet Russia Today, 1947 (Box 9)
    - The Tasks of the Youth Leagues; V. I. Lenin; Foreign Languages Publishing House - Moscow, 1953 (Box 10)
    - Foundations of Leninism; Joseph Stalin; International Publishers, 1939 (Box 10)
    - Mastering Bolshevism; Joseph Stalin; New Century Publishers, August, 1945 (Box 10)
    - Report on Directives of the 20th Congress of the C.P.S.U. for the Sixth Five-Year Plan for the Development of the U.S.S.R 1956-1960); N.A. Bulganin; Foreign Languages Publishing House - Moscow (Box 10)
    - Report of the Central Committee of the Communist Party of the Soviet Union to the 20th Party Congress; N.S. Khrushchov; Foreign Languages Publishing House - Moscow, 1956 (Box 10)
    - Speech at the 20th Congress of the C.P.S.U.; A.I. Kirichenko; Foreign Languages Publishing House - Moscow, 1956 (Box 10)
    - Role of Advanced Ideas in Development of Society; F. Konstantinov; Foreign Languages Publishing House - Moscow, 1954 (Box 10)
    - Speech at the 20th Congress of the C.P.S.U.; M. G. Pervukhin; Foreign Languages Publishing House - Moscow, 1956 (Box 10)
    - Speech at the 20th Congress of the C.P.S.U.; M.A. Suslov; Foreign Languages Publishing House - Moscow, 1956 (Box 10)
    - Economic Problems of Socialism in the U.S.S.R.; Joseph Stalin; International Publishers, 1952 (Box 10)
    - Report to the Nineteenth Party Congress on Amendments to the Rules of the C.P.S.U.(B.); N. Khrushchov; Foreign Languages Publishing House Moscow, 1952 (Box 10)
    - The Nature of Soviet Society; P. F. Yudin; International Publishers, 1951 (Box 10)
    - On the Draft Constitution of the U.S.S.R.; J. V. Stalin; Co-Operative Publishing Society of Foreign Workers in the USSR - Moscow, 1936 (Box 10)
    - Foundations of Leninism; Joseph Stalin; International Publishers, 1932 (Box 10)
    - Political Parties in Russia; Nicholas Lenine; The Socialist Publication Society, Undated (Box 10)
    - The Role of the State in the Socialist Transformation of the Economy of the U.S.S.R; K.V. Ostrovityanov; Foreign Languages Publishing House - Moscow, 1950 (Box 10)
    - In Freedom's Cause: Soviet Youth at War; Fay Caller; New Century Publishers, June, 1943 (Box 10)
    - Russia After Ten Years: Report of the American Trade Union Delegation to the Soviet Union; International Publishers, 1927 (Box 10)
    - Soviet Russia and the Post-War World); Corliss Lamont; National Council of American-Soviet Friendship, Inc, May, 1944 (Box 11)
    - An American Looks at Russia: Can We Live Together in Peace?; Claude Lightfoot New Century Publishers, January, 1951 (Box 11)
    - Lenin on the Woman Question; Clara Zetkin; International Publishers, 1936 (Box 11)
    - Political Economy in the Soviet Union; International Publishers, 1944 (Box 11)
    - Towards Understanding Russia; Rev. George L. Paine; Promoting Enduring Peace, Undated (Box 11)
    - The Sixteen Republics of the Soviet Union; N. Mikhailov; USSR Information Bulletin, 1951 (Box 11)
    - The Soviet People at War; Alvah Bessie; The American Council on Soviet Relations, Undated (Box 11)
    - Russia With Our Own Eyes: Report of the British Workers Delegations, 1950; Srt Publications, Inc., 1951 (Box 11)
    - The State Farms of the U.S.S.R;. P. Lobanov; Foreign Languages Publishing House - Moscow, 1939 (Box 11)
    - The 50th Anniversary of the Communist Party of the Soviet Union (1903-1953); New Century Publishers, September, 1953 (Box 11)
    - The Trade Unions of our Soviet Ally; Clifford T. McAvoy; The American Council on Soviet Relations, 1942 (Box 11)
    - Russia With Our Own Eyes: Report of the British Workers Delegations, 1950; International Publishers, 1927 (Box 11)
    - The Meaning of the XXth Congress of the Communist Party of the Soviet Union; Max Weiss; New Century Publishers, 1956 (Box 11)
    - The Soviet Union: Friend and Ally of the American People; William Z. Foster; International Publishers, October, 1941 (Box 11)
    - Soviet Children and their Care; Rose Maurer National Council of American-Soviet Friendship, Undated (Box 11)
    - Organized Labor in the Soviet Union; Edwin S. Smith; National Council of American-Soviet Friendship, 1943 (Box 11)
    - Inside Russia Today: An Eyewitness Account by a Famous Foreign Correspondent Raymond Arthur Davies; Raymond Arthur Davies; Contemporary Publications, 1945 (Box 11)
    - The Secret of Soviet Strength; Hewlett Johnson; International Publishers, 1943 (Box 11)
    - Debs and Dennis: Fighters for Peace; Elizabeth Gurley Flynn; New Century Publishers, October, 1950 (Box 11)
    - Stages in the History of the Communist Party a Political Review; The Communist, 1941 (Box 11)
    - Our Country Needs a Strong Communist Party; William Z. Foster; New Century Publishers, February, 1956 (Box 11)
    - One War to Defeat Hitler; Robert Minor; International Publishers, November, 1941 (Box 12)
    - Technocracy and Marxism; William Z. Foster & Earl Browder; International Publishers, January, 1933 (Box 12)
    - Science and Religion; Marcel Cachin; International Publishers, 1946 (Box 12)
    - America at the Crossroads: Postwar Problems and Communist Policy; Eugene Dennis; New Century Publishers, December, 1945 (Box 12)
    - The Menace of American Imperialism & America Needs the Communist Party; William Z. Foster & Eugene Dennis; New Century Publishers, October, 1945 (Box 12)
    - Shall the Communist Party Change its Name?; Earl Browder, Eugene Dennis, Roy Hudson, & John WIlliamson; The National Committee, Communist Party, February, 1944 (Box 12)
    - In Defense of Your Freedom: Summation in the Trial of the Eleven Communist Leaders; Eugene Dennis; New Century Publishers, October, 1949 (Box 12)
    - Draft Resolution for the 16th National Convention of the Communist Party, U.S.A; New Century Publishers, 1956 (Box 12)
    - Trotsky Unmasked; Ernst Fischer; International Publishers, May, 1937 (Box 12)
    - "Is Communism a Menace?"; Earl Browder & George E. Sokolsky; New Masses, April, 1943 (Box 12)
    - The Constitution of the Communist Party of the United States of America; International Publishers, Undated (Box 12)
    - The Communist Party and You; Betty Gannet; Communist Party, USA, January, 1947 (Box 12)
    - Lukacs & Socialist Realism: A Hungarian Literary Controversy; Jozsef Revai; Fore Publications, 1950 (Box 12)
    - The Meaning of the 9-Party Communist Conference; William Z. Foster; New Century Publishers, November, 1947 (Box 12)
    - Trotskyism and Fascism; P. Lang; International Publishers, January, 1937 (Box 12)
    - On the Road to Bolshevization; International Publishers, 1929 (Box 12)
    - Party Vigilance: Against Enemy Infiltration; Elmer Larson; New Century Publishers, February, 1953 (Box 12)
    - 1948 Election Platform of the Communist Party; Communist Party, USA, Undated (Box 12)
    - Communists and the People; Elizabeth Gurley Flynn; New Century Publishers, May, 1953 (Box 12)
    - On the Struggle Against Revisionism; Communist Party, USA, January, 1948 (Box 12)
    - Working Class Unity for Peace; New Century Publishers, Undated (Box 12)
    - What it Means to be a Communist; Henry Winston; New Century Publishers, February, 1951 (Box 12)
    - The New Europe; William Z. Foster; International Publishers, 1947 (Box 12)
    - The Communist Party: Vanguard Fighter for Peace, Democracy, Security, Socialism; Pettis Perry; New Century Publishers, April, 1943 (Box 12)
    - Main Political Resolution adopted by the 16th National Convention of the Communist Party, U.S.A; New Century Publishers, 1957 (Box 12)
    - The Communist Political Association; David Goldway; New Century Publishers, Undated (Box 13)
    - Things We Want to Know; Bertram D. Wolfe; Workers Age Publication Association, Undated (Box 13)
    - The Menshevik Trial: The text of the Indictment of the Counter-Revolutionary Menshevik Organization; International Publishers, Undated (Box 13)
    - History of the Working Class: Lesson II the English Industrial Revolution and Chartism; International Publishers, Undated (Box 13)
    - Marxist Study Courses: History of the Working Class; International Publishers, Undated (Box 13)
    - The Communist International; The Communist International, Undated (Box 13)
    - The Communist: Twenty Years of the Communist Party of the U.S.A; Workers Library Publishers, Inc., Undated (Box 13)
    - Why Defend the Rights of Communists?; Herbert Aptheker; New Century Publishers, October, 1949 (Box 13)
    - Communism Versus Fascism; William Z. Foster; Workers Library Publishers, Inc., June, 1941 (Box 13)
    - The Fight for Peace; M. Ercoli; Workers Library Publishers, Inc., November, 1935 (Box 13)
    - Marxism and Modern Art; F. J. Klingender; International Publishers, 1945 (Box 13)
    - The Case for the Communist Party; Eugene Dennis; New Century Publishers, April, 1949 (Box 13)
    - Marx as an Economist; Maurice Dobb International Publishers, 1945 (Box 13)
    - Marxism and Modern Idealism; John Lewis; International Publishers, 1945 (Box 13)
    - Program of the Communist International; International Publishers, 1936 (Box 13)
    - Resolution: Seventh Congress of the Communist International; International Publishers, 1935 (Box 13)
    - The American Way: to Job, Peace, Democracy; New Century Publishers, March, 1954 (Box 14)
    - Theory and Practice of the Communist Party; New Century Publishers, March, 1948 (Box 14)
    - The Menace of American Imperialism & America Needs the Communist Party; William Z Foster & Eugene Dennis; New Century Publishers, October, 1945 (Box 14)
    - Why Communism? Plain Talks on Vital Problems; M. J. Olgin; International Publishers, 1935 (Box 14)
    - Organizing the Party for Victory Over Reaction; Alex Parker; New Century Publishers, 1953 (Box 14)
    - The Communist Party" A Manual on Organization; J. Peters; International Publishers, July, 1935 (Box 14)
    - Constitution of the Communist Party of the United States of America; New Century Publishers, April, 1957 (Box 14)
    - The Paris Commune; Karl Marx; New York Labor News Company, 1941 (Box 14)
    - In Defense of the Communist Party and the Indicted Leaders; William Z. Foster; New Century Publishers, July, 1949 (Box 14)
    - Art Science & Communism; L. Harry Gould; Current Book Distributors, March, 1946 (Box 14)
    - The Present Situation and the Next Tasks; William Z. Foster; New Century Publishers, September, 1945 (Box 14)
    - The Communist Party and You; Betty Gannett; Communist Party, USA, October, 1946 (Box 14)
    - Communism: An Outline for Everyone; R. W. Robson; Communist Party, USA, Undated (Box 14)
    - Communism and Liberty; Wm. Gallacher; Communist Party, USA, Undated (Box 14)
    - The United Front Against Fascism and War; G. Dimitroff; International Publishers, October, 1935 (Box 14)
    - Is Communism Un-American: 9 Questions about the Communist Party Answered; Eugene Dennis; New Century Publishers, March, 1947 (Box 14)
    - Catalogue; New Century Publishers, July, 1950 (Box 14)
    - The Communists Take a New Look: Report to the National Committee of the Communist Party, U.S.A; Eugene Dennis; New Century Publishers, Undated (Box 14)
    - Why I am a Communist; Benjamin J. Davis; New Century Publishers, 1956 (Box 14)
    - Meet the Communists; Elizabeth Gurley Flynn; Communist Party, USA, December, 1947 (Box 14)
    - The Heritage of the Communist Political Association; Robert Minor; International Publishers, March, 1946 (Box 14)
    - The Crime of El Fanguito: An open Letter to President Truman on Puerto Rico; William Z. Foster; New Century Publishers, August, 1944 (Box 14)
    - The War and the Working Class; Georgi Dimitroff; International Publishers, April, 1948 (Box 14)
    - Marxism and Poetry; George Thomson; International Publishers, Undated (Box 14)
    - Marx and Science; J.D. Bernal; International Publishers, 1946 (Box 14)
    - Youth's Road to Peace and Security; Max Weiss; New Age Publishers, 1952 (Box 14)
    - Election Platform of the Communist Party; International Publishers, Undated (Box 14)
    - Declaration of Communist and Workers' Parties of Socialist Countries; New Century Publishers, August, 1940 (Box 14)
    - Marxism-Leninism vs Revisionism; William Z. Foster, Jaques Duclos, Eugene Dennis, John Williamson; New Century Publishers, December, 1957 (Box 14)
    - Grasp the Weapon of Culture!; V. J. Jerome; New Century Publishers, February, 1946 (Box 14)
    - The Two Worlds; International Publishers, 1940 (Box 15)
    - Communism versus Fascism; William Z. Foster; International Publishers, 1935 (Box 15)
    - Marxist Study Courses: History of the Working Class; International Publishers, 1941 (Box 15)
    - The Communist; International Publishers, Undated (Box 15)
    - Ideas They Cannot Jail; Eugene Dennis; International Publishers, November, 1935 (Box 15)
    - The Thought of Mao Tse-Tung; Anna Louise Strong, 1950 (Box 15)
    - The Sleepy Lagoon Case; The Mercury Printing Co, Undated (Box 15)
    - Food Prices and Rationing; Louise Mitchell; International Publishers, September, 1943 (Box 15)
    - Verdict Against Freedom: Your Stake in the Communist Trial; Joseph North; New Century Publishers, January, 1943 (Box 15)
    - Who are the Foreign Agents?; Lawrence Mahan; Communist Party, USA, November,1949 (Box 15)
    - I Charge "Frame-Up"; Al Lannon; Maritime Labor Committee to Defend Al Lannon, June, 1948 (Box 15)
    - Are We Being Talked into War?; Corliss Lamont, Undated (Box 15)
    - To the Farmer from His Customers; Department of Education and Research Congress of Industrial Organizations, Undated (Box 15)
    - "Let's Come out Fighting!"; Henry A. Wallace; The United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America, CIO, Undated (Box 15)
    - Politics for Progress 1954; C.B. Baldwin, Undated (Box 15)
    - Youth Builds a Railway; The British Yugoslav Association, Undated (Box 15)
    - Foreign-Born Americans and the War; Louis Adamic & George F. Addes; American Committee For the Protection of Foreign Born, April, 1947 (Box 15)
    - The Challenge of the '56 Elections: Report to the National Committee of the Communist Party, U.S.A; Claude Lightfoot; New Century Publishers, Undated (Box 15)
    - What's Behind the Berlin Crisis; Joseph Clark; New Century Publishers, 1956 (Box 15)
    - Turning Point for the World; R. Palme Dutt; International Publishers, August, 1948 (Box 15)
    - What's Behind "Juvenile Delinquency"; Aaron Weissman; New Century Publishers, September, 1941 (Box 15)
    - Amnesty!; Marion Bachrach; New Century Publishers, May, 1955 (Box 15)
    - How to Keep Your Job: Must We Have Depression? ;Bernard Burton; New Century Publishers, May, 1943 (Box 15)
    - Who Pays for the Cold War? How the Marshall Plan Affects Your Living Standards; George Blake; New Century Publishers, February, 1955 (Box 15)
    - The Deportation Drive vs. The Bill of Rights; Abner Green; New Century Publishers, May, 1949 (Box 15)
    - Food Now or Coffins Later the Meaning of the World Food Crisis; Charles J. Cole; Farm Research, February, 1941 (Box 15)
    - Truman's 81st Congress; Rob Fowler Hall; New Century Publishers, July, 1956 (Box 15)
    - Your Stake in the Elections; Adam Lapin; International Publishers, August, 1949 (Box 15)
    - Should Americans Back the Marshall Plan?; Joseph Starobin; New Century Publishers, September, 1944 (Box 15)
    - The Truth About the Prague Trial; Louis Harap; Jewish Life, February, 1948 (Box 15)
    - We Can Have Peace and Jobs!; Bernard Burton; New Century Publishers, 1953 (Box 15)
    - Depression: Hard Facts Vs. Soft Soap; Joseph Morton; The Pacific Publishing Foundation, March, 1953 (Box 15)
    - Syndicalism; Earl C. Ford & William Z. Foster; William Z. Foster, Undated (Box 15)
    - The Intervention in Siberia 1918-1922; V. Parfenov; International Publishers, Undated (Box 15)
    - The Cartel System; James S. Allen; International Publishers, June, 1941 (Box 15)
    - Neither to Right nor Left; William O. Douglas; CIO Publications Department, 1946 (Box 15)
    - Grasp the Weapon of Culture!; V. J. Jerome; New Century Publishers, Undated (Box 15)
    - The November Elections and the Fight for Jobs, Peace, Equal Rights, Democracy; Pettis Perry; New Century Publishers, December, 1951 (Box 15)
    - Dear Unknown Friend; National Council of American-Soviet Friendship, September, 1954 (Box 15)
    - Congress and You; Frank Ryhlick; International Publishers, June, 1943 (Box 16)
    - The People Against the Trusts; Eugene Dennis; New Century Publishers, December, 1946 (Box 16)
    - The "Free Press": Portrait of a Monopoly; George Marion; New Century Publishers, June, 1946 (Box 16)
    - The Deportation Terror: A Weapon to Gag America; Abner Green; New Century Publishers, January, 1950 (Box 16)
    - Amnesty!; Marion Bachrach; New Century Publishers, December, 1952 (Box 16)
    - What America Faces: The New War Danger and the Struggle for Peace, Democracy and Economic Security; Eugene Dennis; New Century Publishers, March, 1946 (Box 16)
    - The History of May Day; Alexander Trachtenberg; International Publishers, Undated (Box 16)
    - The Deportation Drive Vs. The Bill of Rights: The McCarran Act and the Foreign Born; Abner Green, February, 1951 (Box 16)
    - The North Atlantic Pact: For Peace or War?; Abraham Chapman; New Century Publishers, May, 1949 (Box 16)
    - Marshall Plan-Recovery or War?; James S. Allen; New Century Publishers, April, 1948 (Box 16)
    - The Meaning of the Soviet Trials; E. Yaroslavsky; International Publishers, March, 1938 (Box 16)
    - At the Moscow Trial; D. N. Pritt, & K.C., M.P., 1937 (Box 16)
    - The Answer is Full Employment; Joseph Gaer & Robert K. Lamb; CIO Political Action Committee, Undated (Box 16)
    - Renconversion:60,000,000 Jobs or 15,000,000 Jobless; George Morris New Century Publishers, September, 1945 (Box 16)
    - Toward Singing Tomorrows: The Last Testament of Gabriel Peri; Gabriel Peri & Louis Aragon; International Publishers, 1946 (Box 16)
    - The Schlesinger Fraud: A Critique of the "Third Force in America"; Herbert Aptheker; Masses & Mainstream, Inc., November, 1949 (Box 16)
    - When He Comes Back If He Comes Back Nervous: Two talks to families of returning Servicemen; Thomas A. C. Rennie, M.D. & Luther. E. Woodward, Ph.D.; The National Committee for Mental Hygiene, Inc., Undated (Box 16)
    - If This Be Treason; Richard O. Boyer; New Century Publishers, December, 1948 (Box 16)
    - William Z. Foster: An Appreciation; Joseph North; International Publishers, 1955 (Box 16)
    - Appeal International Initiative Committee, 1952 (Box 16)
    - Biddle's Private War against Harry Bridges; Harry Bridges Victory Committee, Undated (Box 16)
    - Eisler Hits Back; The German American Inc., Undated (Box 16)
    - The Devil and Jimmy Byrnes; Frederick L. Schuman; Soviet Russia Today, 1948 (Box 16)
    - Due Process in a Political Trial: The Record vs. The Press; National Nonpartisan Committee, Undated (Box 16)
    - Koje: Unscreened; Wilfred Burchett & Alan Winnington; Britain-China Friendship Association, Undated (Box 16)